(Sheldon-bot:)Using Photoshop, I've
introduced a few anachronisms.
(Sheldon-bot:)See if you can spot all 24.
(Sheldon-bot:)I'll give you the first one.
(Sheldon-bot:)Madame Curie should not
be wearing a digital watch.
(Sheldon-bot:)And go.
(Leonard:)That's it. Bye-bye.
(Sheldon-bot(screen switching itself back on):)Bazinga.
Whoa!
(Sheldon-bot:)I have an override switch.
(Leonard:)I almost died!
(Sheldon-bot :)And I'm safe and sound in bed.
(Sheldon-bot :)Who's crazy now?
(Leonard:)I'm still going
to go with you.
(Sheldon-bot :)Hello, Professor Hoskins.
(Sheldon-bot :)Nice to see you, Mindy.
And konnichiwa, Dr. Nakamora.
(Sheldon-bot :)Sorry the Swedes
disproved your theory.